ireff.in 2019-06-30

# Privacy policy

**_PRIVACY POLICY_**

iReff is committed to your privacy vis-à-vis the protection of your information. In order to endow you with our uninterrupted use of services, we may collect and, in some circumstances, disclose information about you. To enhance better protection of your privacy we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**_OVERVIEW_**

We commit to respecting your online data privacy. We further recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (" **Personal Information** ") you share with us. Information that is considered personal about you by us includes, but is not limited to, your name, address, email address or other contact information. 

In order to use this website or App, you may be required to register yourself by providing the following information which includes, but is not limited to:

(1) Name;

(2) User name;

(3) Password;

(4) Mobile number;

(5) Telecom Operator;

(6) Telecom Circle;

(7) Gender; 

(8) Address; etc.

Kindly note that the list above is merely illustrative only and that you may be required to provide other information during registration.

**_NOTIFICATION OF MODIFICATIONS AND CHANGES TO THE T &C AND PRIVACY POLICY_**

We reserve the right to change the Terms and Privacy Policy from time to time as seen fit, without any intimation to you, and your continued use of the site or App will signify your acceptance of any amendment to these terms.

You are therefore advised to re-read the Terms of Service and Privacy Policy on a regular basis. Should it be that you do not accept any of the modifications or amendments to the Terms, you may terminate your use of this website and app on mobile devices immediately.

**_INFORMATION WE COLLECT_**

Our site's or App’s online registration form requires users to give us contact information (like your name, address, telephone number and email address), and demographic information (like your zip code/pin code). As a member you are required to provide a valid email address at registration and choose a username or alias that represents your identity on our website and app on mobile devices. 

**_COOKIES_**

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" (small pieces of data we store for an extended period of time on your computer, mobile phone, or other device) on certain pages of our websites and in App, for providing customized services. We also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". Cookies can also help us provide information, which is targeted to your interests. Cookies may be used whether you register with us or not.

**_EXTERNAL LINKS ON WEBSITE_**

The Website and App may include hyperlinks to other web sites or references to other apps or other content or resources. We have no control over any websites, apps or resources, which are provided by companies or persons other than Us.

You acknowledge and agree that We are not responsible for the availability of any such external sites or resources, and do not endorse any advertising, products or other materials on or available from such websites or resources.

You acknowledge and agree that We are not liable for any loss or damage which may be incurred by you as a result of the availability of those external sites or resources, or as a result of any reliance placed by you on the completeness, accuracy or existence of any advertising, products or other materials on, or available from, such websites or resources. These third-party service providers and Third-Party Sites may have their own privacy policies governing the storage and retention of your personal information that you may be subject to. We recommend that when you enter a Third-Party Site, you review the Third Party Site’s privacy policy as it relates to safeguarding your personal information. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website and app on mobile devices. 

Our website and app will have social media widgets, share links and small programs, which are hosted by third party or us. These features may collect your IP address and track your usage and set some cookies to function properly. Your interactions with these social media features are governed by the privacy policy of those companies providing it.

**_OUR USE OF YOUR INFORMATION_**

Your contact information is used to contact you when necessary. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. We may use your IP address to help protect our partners and ourselves from fraud.

We may release your personal information to a third-party in order comply with a Court Order or other similar legal procedure, or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law; prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or investigate or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or violations of Our Terms of Use. We may disclose certain information about you, your recharge information and data analytics to our business partners. ****

By way of example (without limiting and foregoing), third parties may sometimes unlawfully intercept or access transmissions, or other parties may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our Websites. Therefore, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that any information that we collect about you or private communications would always remain private.

The Website and App may show ads from Facebook. For more details on Facebook ads please see https://m.facebook.com/ads/ad_choices 

The website also has enabled the Google Analytics Advertising and User ID Feature, which allows Google to collect data about users on our website, in addition to Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers. You may choose to opt out of this by downloading and installing the Google Analytics opt-out add-on [ https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). However, we will not share or upload any of your personally identifiable information on these tools. 

From time to time, we may run promotional reward programs using third party tools. We may share your personal information with these partners for the purpose of communicating reward status back to you, and also for routine fraud detection. 

**_ACCESSING, REVIEWING AND CHANGING YOUR PROFILE_**

Following registration, you can review and change the information you submitted except your display name, during registration. If you change any information we may keep track of your old information. You can change your registration information such as: name, address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, and profile.

To remove your profile so that others cannot view it, contact our customer support team at care@ireff.in.

We will retain in our files information you have requested to remove for certain circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions. Further, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored 'back up' systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

**_OTHER INFORMATION COLLECTORS_**

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are on our Websites or App or on other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies. Since we do not control the privacy policies of the third parties, you are subject to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should contact our Customer Support Desk at care@ireff.in
